let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What doeas HTML stand for?",
        answer: "C. Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "A. Hyper Type Multi Language",
            "B. Hyper Text Multiple Language",
            "C. Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "D. Home Text Multi Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What do you understand by HTML?",
        answer: "D. All of the above",
        options: [
            "A. HTML describes the structure of a webpage",
            "B. HTML is the standard markup language mainly used to create web pages",
            "C. HTML consists of a set of elements that helps the browser how to view the content",
            "D. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Who is the father of HTML?",
        answer: "B. Tim Berners-Lee",
        options: [
            "A. Rasmus Lerdorf",
            "B. Tim Berners-Lee",
            "C. Brendan Eich",
            "D. Sergey Brin"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which is used to read an HTML page and render it?",
        answer: "C. Web browser",
        options: [
            "A. Web server",
            "B. Web network",
            "C. Web browser",
            "D. Web matrix"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which tag is used for inserting the largest heading in HTML?",
        answer: "B. h1",
        options: [
            " A. head",
            "B. h1",
            "C. h6",
            "D. heading"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which is used to create Web Pages ?",
        answer: "C. HTML",
        options: [
            " A. C++",
            "B. Java",
            "C. HTML",
            "D. JVM"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "HTML is a set of markup ___.",
        answer: "A. tags",
        options: [
            "A. tags",
            "B. sets",
            "C. attributes",
            "D. none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "HTML tags are used to describe document ___.",
        answer: "B. content",
        options: [
            " A. definition",
            "B. content",
            "C. language",
            "D. model"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "HTML program is saved using ___ extension.",
        answer: "B. .html",
        options: [
            " A. .htmn",
            "B. .html",
            "C. .htnl",
            "D. .htnl"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "HTML program can be read and rendered by ___.",
        answer: "C. Web Browser",
        options: [
            " A. Compiler",
            "B. Server",
            "C. Web Browser",
            "D. Interpreter"
        ]
    }
]
